hi welcome to another video so deep seek
V3 has been recently launched and it's a
really good model especially because
it's fully open weights and their API is
dirt cheap which is pretty great to see
not just that you can currently use the
Deep seek V3 model for free via
hyperbolic yes although you won't see
deep seek in hyperbolic model section
yet they are providing the model for
free through their
API it's a little unstable for now and
until it gets added to the platform
officially it seems to be free which is
great so that's super great and many
people were asking me how they can
create agents with the new deep seek V3
model to accomplish tasks that are
needed in any custom workflow you'd like
for it to
do well that's what I'm going to show
you today most people want to make these
AI agents easily as well without messing
around with anything locally and stuff
like
that so to keep everything simple we'll
be using Vector
shift if you don't know about Vector
shift I have some other great videos
about it as well but in general terms
it's an AI automation platform that
allows you to make workflows where you
can connect any data source source to AI
create custom workflows and build AI
agents that you need like if you want an
AI agent that can summarize your Google
calendar events you can do that or if
you want an AI agent that reads your
notion notes and summarizes them for you
it can do that as well you can also put
these workflows in a chat bot and you
can also access these workflows via
apis not just that you can also automate
like making your workflows trigger when
you send a message in Discord receive an
email or something like
that so that's super cool as well now
let me tell you how you can configure it
all and create agents with the new deep
seek V3 platform so just get yourself
signed up here it also has a free tier
which is good anyway once you're here
you can just go to pipelines Pipelines
are the major stuff and everything else
is dependent on this now just hit the
new button and it will open up this page
where you can select from some pre-built
workflows or you can just hit this and
it will open up a new
canvas here you can drag in the blocks
you want to connect and create your own
workflow so let's say that we are
creating a simple
chatbot well in that case we'll first
need to drag in an input here this will
allow the user to give input now we can
connect this input to something like an
llm or a knowledge base where you can
easily make a user input query a
knowledge base and give the required
context from that knowledge base or you
can also connect it to some other
integration but because we are creating
a simple chatbot let's add an llm here
now in llms you have multiple options
like open AI anthropic perplexity or
something like that now to use deep seek
we can just drag in the custom one here
and enter the Deep seek or hyperbolic
API base URL model name and API key
based on what you want to
use once that's done you can connect
your input to it and also enter the
system prompt once done you can just
drag in the output and then connect it
to the
llm now you have a basic workflow that
takes input runs it through an llm and
gives you the
output now you can add whatever you want
to this workflow as well let's say you
want the AI agent here to have the
context of your notion
notes you can just drag the notion
integration in and connect it in the
workflow as you'd like and your llm will
have access to that which is
great you can even add search or some
other llm and Route some requests to
that llm based on if else
logic this allows you to delegate
specific tasks to another llm or do some
other kind of flow which is all super
great you can also test the pipelines as
you make them by clicking this button
and just entering the input and testing
it through
here this will allow you to check
everything before you deploy it as an
API or chatbot or anything like
that so that's also
cool once you have everything figured
out you can just click the deploy
changes option and it will save your
workflow then you can just export it to
be an automation chatbot search or form
which is pretty great let's select
chatbot now once you select it you can
just enter the chatbot name
and then go to the next page here you
can configure stuff like how you want
the chatbot to look and things like that
once done you can just deploy the
chatbot integrate it anywhere or use it
as an API in your own
applications or you can also just chat
with the chatbot here which is also
great to see so that's how you can
configure an AI agent with deep seek
easily via Vector shift
apart from this you can also create
automations with it automations are
basically a way to trigger the workflow
you've made via something that happens
in another
application for example if you want your
workflow to be triggered when you send a
message in some slack Channel you can do
that quite easily here which is pretty
great there are also options to add
knowledge to your AI agents you can just
upload the files that your AI agent can
reference and and take in your custom
knowledge-based context which is also
pretty great you can also create voice
spots bulk jobs portals evaluations and
stuff like that which is great so that's
how you can easily create AI agents with
deep seeks new model it's super cool to
use for these kinds of workflow
automations because it is super cheap
and it allows you to get the same
performance as Claude in in these tasks
for super cheap which is
great you can also add search any kind
of apps knowledge base and stuff which
makes it so cool it's all in a drag and
drop interface that allows you to
customize it in any way you want and use
it all for free via something like
hyperbolic with Vector shift and it will
all be
free overall it's pretty
cool anyway let me know your thoughts in
the comments ments if you liked this
video consider donating to my Channel
Through the super thanks option below or
you can also consider becoming a member
by clicking the join
button also give this video a thumbs up
and subscribe to my channel I'll see you
in the next video till then bye